<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Auxillium</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="editText">Technovation 2020!</string>
    <string name="SophiesButton">Sophies button</string>
    <string name="AnirrasButton">Anirras Button</string>
    <string name="profileButton">Profile</string>
    <string name="infoButton">Info</string>
    <string name="settingsButton">Settings</string>
    <string name="Register">Register</string>
    <string name="infoPage">this is info page</string>
    <string name="levelNumberHome">Level 1: Shooting</string>
    <string name="categoryHome">Public Disasters</string>
    <string name="Email">Email</string>
    <string name="Password">Password</string>
    <string name="Username">Username</string>
    <string name="Name">Name</string>
    <string name="signUp">Sign Up</string>
    <integer name="myScore">0</integer>
    <string name="buttonEarthquake">Earthquake</string>
    <string name="ReTakeQuiz">Retake Quiz</string>
    <string name="Blank">Blank</string>
    <string name="articlesTitle">Informational Articles</string>
    <string name="article1">Harmful Psychological Effects of Racial Stereotyping</string>
    <string name="article2">LGBTQ Definitions Every Good Ally Should Know</string>
    <string name="article3">Interacting with People with Disabilities</string>
    <string name="article4">The Dos and Don\'ts of Cultural Appropriation</string>



    <string name="CPRtext">CPR</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="open_game">Open Game</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="NextButton">NEXT</string>
    <string name="TakeQuiz">TAKE QUIZ</string>

    <string name="PurchaseButton">Purchase</string>
    <string name="character1Cost">100 coins</string>
    <string name="character2Cost">200 coins</string>
    <string name="character3Cost">300 coins</string>
    <string name="character4Cost">400 coins</string>
    <string name="character5Cost">500 coins</string>
    <string name="characterPurchased">This character has been purchased!</string>
    <string name="shopTitle">Character Shop</string>

    <string name="openRequestForm">Submit an article request</string>





    //Simran Jeet Singh Strings

    <string name="SimranTitle">Simran Jeet Singh</string>
    <string name="SimranBio"> An activist who advocates for religious equality in America
        Gender: Male
        Pronouns: He/Him
        Age: 36
        Race: American</string>
    <string name="SimranInfo1">Simran Jeet Singh was born on July 25, 1984, in San Antonio, Texas. Growing up, there were not a lot of Sikh families where he lived and his parents felt it was important to stay connected to their culture. Singh started learning Punjabi from a young age and also consistently did kirtan and ardas (religious practices) , as there were no Gurdwaras (Sikh places of worship) where he lived. His community was small and they met on Friday nights but Singh also had friends who weren’t Sikh. He felt like he was living in two different worlds.

        Singh went to camps around America during the years that were connected with Sikhi but he didn’t feel truly (tied) until he started learning about the recent history of his people. He learned he was named by his parents after a famous political activist at the time. From these places came his inspiration to help his community. From his emotional connections came his spiritual connections to the world.
    </string>
    <string name="SimranInfo2"> After 9/11, Singh realized that identity includes how other people view you as well as how you view yourself. He saw himself being grouped into places while his community was turning invisible, trying to explain their story. 9/11 showed him the pain and ignorance people show towards certain religions and faiths. He felt he had the responsibility and privilege, that others didn’t have, to change that.

    Today, Simran Jeet Singh is a writer, a professor at Columbia University, and a Senior Religion Fellow for the Sikh Coalition, and a Truman National Security Fellow for the Truman National Security Project. He has multiple degrees from Harvard and Columbia University and has a podcast called Spirited where he talks about leaders and activists. He has also written a book called Fauja Singh Keeps Going about the oldest person who was believed to run a marathon. He lives with his two children and his wife.
    </string>
    <string name="SimranReferences">http://www.wearesikhs.org/simran_jeet_singh
    https://theconversation.com/profiles/simran-jeet-singh-486698#:~:text=Born%20and%20raised%20in%20San,at%20Weill%20Cornell%20Medical%20College.</string>


    //Simran Jeet Singh Quiz

    <string name="Q1Simran">1. Where was Singh born where there were not many Sikh families at the time?</string>
    <string name="Q1_A1Simran">Antipolo, Philippines</string>
    <string name="Q1_A2Simran">Sacramento, California</string>
    <string name="Q1_A3Simran">Mingora, Swat valley, Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Q1_A4Simran">San Antonio, Texas</string>

    <string name="Q2Simran">2. When did Simran Jeet Singh begin feeling truly tied to the culture of his people?</string>
    <string name="Q2_A1Simran">When he started going to Gurdwaras at a young age</string>
    <string name="Q2_A2Simran">When he began learning about the recent history of his people</string>
    <string name="Q2_A3Simran">When 9/11 occurred</string>
    <string name="Q2_A4Simran">When he performed religious practices with his family</string>

    <string name="Q3Simran">3. Who was Simran Jeet Singh named after?</string>
    <string name="Q3_A1Simran">A famous singer at the time</string>
    <string name="Q3_A2Simran">A famous drum player at the time</string>
    <string name="Q3_A3Simran">A famous political activist at the time</string>
    <string name="Q3_A4Simran"> A famous painter at the time</string>

    <string name="Q4Simran">4. What did Singh see after 9/11?</string>
    <string name="Q4_A1Simran">He saw himself being grouped into places while his community was turning invisible</string>
    <string name="Q4_A2Simran">He saw himself being more ignorant towards people of other races</string>
    <string name="Q4_A3Simran">He saw large amounts of others grouping themselves into certain religious categories</string>
    <string name="Q4_A4Simran">He saw that all races and religions were treated equally</string>

    <string name="Q5Simran">5. What is Simran Jeet Singh’s podcast “Spirited” about?</string>
    <string name="Q5_A1Simran">His favorite books about painting</string>
    <string name="Q5_A2Simran">Leaders and activists</string>
    <string name="Q5_A3Simran">Political parties in America</string>
    <string name="Q5_A4Simran">His favorite foods</string>


    //Alice Wong Strings

    <string name="AliceTitle">Alice Wong</string>
    <string name="AliceBio"> Pronouns: She/Her Gender: Female Age: 46 Activist for the rights of disabled people </string>
    <string name="AliceInfo1">Alice Wong was born in Indianapolis, Indiana on March 24, 1974, with Spinal Muscular Atrophy (SMA). As a young girl, she always felt lonely being a wheel-chair user. It was a three-hour drive from her home to buy lunch and groceries as Chinese-Americans living in Indiana. She found the distance made her appreciate the food more. She also experienced bullying at schools. Her classmates would push her and hit her because she was weak and her teachers did not make enough accommodations for people with disabilities.
        Wong became a sociologist and learned about different groups and what they meant. From there, she started thinking about disabilities as less of just a biological difference but also how it affected people mentally. She found she had a lot of anger due to her disability which she started channeling into writing and research. She experienced microaggressions from others towards people with disabilities such as when she was denied a drama course because she would not be able to be “physical enough”.
    </string>
    <string name="AliceInfo2"> In early 2014, she started developing the Disability Visibility Project after she attended a StoryCorps event in San Francisco for animated portions on NPR’s Morning Edition. She found it left a lasting impression on her and reached out to someone to ask if they were interested in creating a project with a disability community-specific partnership. The project was launched in July 2014 to help document the experiences of people with disabilities.
        Wong has also written an essay published in Amerasia Journal, “Musings from an Angry Asian American Disabled Girl”, where she wrote about her experiences growing up. She strives to connect young women and girls with disabilities to empower them.
    </string>
    <string name="AliceReferences">https://letterstothrive.tumblr.com/post/55608302401/hey-angry-girl  https://www.easterseals.com/thrive/who-we-are/alice-wong.html  https://disabilityvisibilityproject.com/2015/12/12/dvp-interview-alice-wong-and-ellen-wu/</string>


    //Alice Wong Quiz

    <string name="Q1Alice">1. What condition was Alice Wong born with?</string>
    <string name="Q1_A1Alice">Autism Spectrum Disorder</string>
    <string name="Q1_A2Alice">Spinal Muscular Atrophy</string>
    <string name="Q1_A3Alice">Kernicterus</string>
    <string name="Q1_A4Alice">Myotonic dystrophy</string>

    <string name="Q2Alice">2. How did becoming a sociologist influence Wong\’s thinking?</string>
    <string name="Q2_A1Alice">She started thinking about disabilities as not only a biological difference but also how they affected people mentally</string>
    <string name="Q2_A2Alice">She started thinking about how race influenced the way people thought of disabilities</string>
    <string name="Q2_A3Alice">She started thinking about the way that the food people ate influenced their disabilities</string>
    <string name="Q2_A4Alice">She started thinking about disabilities as not only a biological difference but also thinking about how they affected people politically</string>

    <string name="Q3Alice">3. In which experience did Wong feel a micro-aggression towards people with disabilities?</string>
    <string name="Q3_A1Alice">When her teacher told her she could not play in the soccer game because she was not strong enough</string>
    <string name="Q3_A2Alice">When her best friend told her they couldn\’t be friends because she wasn\’t smart enough</string>
    <string name="Q3_A3Alice">When her sister told her that she could not go shopping with her because she wasn\’t pretty enough</string>
    <string name="Q3_A4Alice">When she was denied a drama course because they said she would not be able to be physical enough</string>

    <string name="Q4Alice">4. What is the Disability Visibility Project?</string>
    <string name="Q4_A1Alice">A project Alice Wong developed to help people see again</string>
    <string name="Q4_A2Alice">A project Wong\’s sister developed to connect people with disabilities to connect them to people in senior centers</string>
    <string name="Q4_A3Alice">A project Alice Wong developed to allow people to learn about the stories of people with disabilities</string>
    <string name="Q4_A4Alice">A project Alice Wong developed for student’s to raise awareness about climate change</string>

    <string name="Q5Alice">5. What is Alice Wong\’s essay in Amerasia Journal, “Musings from an Angry Asian American Disabled Girl” about?</string>
    <string name="Q5_A1Alice">Her experiences as a disabled Asian American growing up</string>
    <string name="Q5_A2Alice">Her story about someone knocking over her basket in a grocery store</string>
    <string name="Q5_A3Alice">Her story about creating her own school</string>
    <string name="Q5_A4Alice">Her experiences growing up in a busy city</string>


    //Thandiwe Abdullah Strings

    <string name="ThandiweTitle">Thandiwe Abdullah</string>
    <string name="ThandiweBio"> Pronouns: She/Her Gender: Female Age: 17 Activist for anti-racism and equality movements</string>
    <string name="ThandiweInfo1">Thandiwe Abdullah was born in the Crenshaw District Los Angeles California in 2003. She was born to an activist family and started attending Black Lives Matter meetings at the young age of 10. Along with this, she was raised by many strong African American women in her community. Her mom was a professor of Pan African Studies at CSULA and she later (became) a co-founder of the LA chapter of Black Lives Matter. The founders of the Black Lives Matter Movement, Patrisse Kahn Cullors, Opal Tometti, and Alicia Garza, taught her to expand her thinking. She learned about pronouns, gender fluidity, and more about African American culture. However, Abdullah realized that she and her siblings were the only children being raised by the movement despite its goal to encourage a family community.
        She felt the effects of colorism, being called prettier because she was “lighter-skinned” and realized that lighter skin girls were more heard. In school, she felt as if she was fitting into the “angry Black girl mold” that society perpetuated. People around her wanted her to stop but she would not stop her activism and calling people out on their racism.
    </string>
    <string name="ThandiweInfo2"> She felt she did not fit into the women’s rights movement, that it was just white women who talked about microaggressions and the wage gap. However, she noticed that African American women get paid 21% less than an average white woman. She wanted to bring to light the privilege that some people have that others do not and to make sure movements reflect all people they stand for.
        Today, Abdullah says she works for all her sisters and people of color. She is an activist in the Black Lives Matter movement and a co-founder of Black Lives Matter Youth Vanguard which is a program to help Black youth, specifically in the LA area. She is greatly dedicated to her activism and changing the world to make sure no one has to worry about affording basic human needs.
    </string>
    <string name="ThandiweReferences">https://www.seventeen.com/life/a34717855/thandiwe-abdullah-black-lives-matter-voices-of-the-year-2020/</string>

    //Thandiwe Abdullah Quiz Strings

    <string name="Q1Thandiwe">1. At what age did Abdullah begin attending Black Lives Matter meetings?</string>
    <string name="Q1_A1Thandiwe">20</string>
    <string name="Q1_A2Thandiwe">17</string>
    <string name="Q1_A3Thandiwe">6</string>
    <string name="Q1_A4Thandiwe">10</string>

    <string name="Q2Thandiwe">2. What did she learn from the founders of the Black Lives Matter Movement (Patrisse Kahn Cullors, Opal Tometti, and Alicia Garza)?</string>
    <string name="Q2_A1Thandiwe">Pronouns, gender fluidity, and African American culture</string>
    <string name="Q2_A2Thandiwe">How to read and speak English</string>
    <string name="Q2_A3Thandiwe">How to recognize when someone has a disability</string>
    <string name="Q2_A4Thandiwe">Asian American culture and the differences in languages around the globe</string>

    <string name="Q3Thandiwe">3. Which mold did Abdullah say she felt like she was being put into at school?</string>
    <string name="Q3_A1Thandiwe">“angry Black girl”</string>
    <string name="Q3_A2Thandiwe">“smart Asian boy”</string>
    <string name="Q3_A3Thandiwe">“unintelligent Black girl”	</string>
    <string name="Q3_A4Thandiwe">“cheerful American boy”</string>

    <string name="Q4Thandiwe">4. What did Abdullah want to bring to light after learning about after learning that an African American woman gets paid 21% less than an average white woman despite feeling like the majority of the women\'s rights movement?</string>
    <string name="Q4_A1Thandiwe">The money that others have that they can give to immigrants</string>
    <string name="Q4_A2Thandiwe">The privilege that others have that they should not use because it is not fair to others</string>
    <string name="Q4_A3Thandiwe">The education that some people have that others do not that they should use to teach seniors.</string>
    <string name="Q4_A4Thandiwe">The privilege that some people have that others do not and to make sure movements reflect all people they stand for</string>

    <string name="Q5Thandiwe">5. What is the Black Lives Matter Youth Vanguard?</string>
    <string name="Q5_A1Thandiwe">A program to help Asian</string>
    <string name="Q5_A2Thandiwe">A program to help Black youth</string>
    <string name="Q5_A3Thandiwe">A program to help disabled youth</string>
    <string name="Q5_A4Thandiwe">A program to help immigrants</string>

    //Beverly Palesa Ditsie Strings

    <string name="BeverlyTitle">Beverly Palesa Ditsie</string>
    <string name="BeverlyBio"> Pronouns: She/Her Gender: Female Age: 50 Activist for LGBTQ+ rights</string>
    <string name="BeverlyInfo1">Beverly Palesa Ditsie was born in 1970 in Soweto, South Africa. From the age of 10, she acted in movies as an actress and voice actor. She grew up in her grandmother’s home and always felt like she was surrounded by love there. Her grandmother was a rock to her, a pillar of the community as she watched her struggle  but pursue. She also valued her grandmother’s husband and her mother a lot.
        Ditsie’s call to activism was when she became a student council representative in her high school. She always thought that there was an “overpowering” masculinity that surrounded the system. She was frustrated and spent a lot of time with queer boys, starting with them their first meeting of Glow [the Gay and Lesbian Organisation of the Witwatersrand]. There she met Simon Nkoli who she later directed the movie Simon and I about. He was an older brother figure to her who helped raise voices for the LQBTQA+ community. Glow was deeply rooted in intersectionality. In NGO spaces, Ditsie began to make sure all voices were included and pointed out deep exclusion in communities.
    </string>
    <string name="BeverlyInfo2">Glow helped wth the formation of the National Coalition for Gay and Lesbian Equality (NCGLE) which ensured that rights based on gender and sexuality were included in South Africa’s new constitution at the time. Ditsie spoke at the 1995 United Nations Conference on Women in Bejing, being the first person, an African lesbian woman to talk, about LGBTQA+ rights at a UN Convention. She spoke about how discrimination based on sexual orientation was a violation of basic human rights and it was neccessary to address that before talking about any other concerns of women. Ditsie struggled with her mental health through her activism, living through apartheid, and the imposter syndrome she experienced because of her gender.
        Ditsie continued making films to bring attention to people in the LGBTQA+ community and people with HIV/AIDs. Her film Simon and I became very popular and displayed a clear message about what she fought for, freedom. Today she continues her activism to inspire and help others. In 2019, she was a recipient of an honorary degree from Claremont Graduate University in California, United States for her activism and fight to bring justice to people in society.
    </string>
    <string name="BeverlyReferences">https://sandtonchronicle.co.za/lnn/299767/celebrating-bev-ditsie-for-her-role-in-making-lgbti-rights-a-reality
    https://lovemattersafrica.com/sexual-diversity/beverly-palesa-ditsie-a-pioneer-for-african-intersectionality
    https://www.wmm.com/filmmaker/Beverley+Palesa+Ditsie/
    https://www.sahistory.org.za/dated-event/beverly-palesa-ditsie-first-out-lesbian-woman-address-united-nations-about-lgbt-rights
    https://www.theguardian.com/society/2020/aug/20/beverley-ditsie-the-south-african-woman-who-helped-liberate-lesbians-everywhere
    https://www.newframe.com/beverley-ditsie-comes-full-circle/</string>

    <string name="Q1Beverly">1. What was Ditsie\’s call to activism?</string>
    <string name="Q1_A1Beverly">When her best friend became an activist for Disability rights</string>
    <string name="Q1_A2Beverly">When she attended one of her school’s GLOW club meetings and felt she had a responsibility to start her own club</string>
    <string name="Q1_A3Beverly">When she became a student council representative in her high school because she thought that there was “overpowering” masculinity that surrounded the system</string>
    <string name="Q1_A4Beverly">When her grandmother died and she felt she could never be like her</string>

    <string name="Q2Beverly">2. Who was a mentor to Ditsie that guided her in her fight for LGBTQ+ rights?</string>
    <string name="Q2_A1Beverly">Laverne Cox</string>
    <string name="Q2_A2Beverly">Simon Nkoli</string>
    <string name="Q2_A3Beverly">Bruce Wayne</string>
    <string name="Q2_A4Beverly">Anne Hathaway</string>

    <string name="Q3Beverly">3. What is the National Coalition for Gay and Lesbian Equality (NCGLE)?</string>
    <string name="Q3_A1Beverly">An organization that brought light to LGBTQ+ issues in senior centers</string>
    <string name="Q3_A2Beverly">An organization that ensured that rights based on gender and sexuality were included in South Africa’s new constitution at the time</string>
    <string name="Q3_A3Beverly">An organization that ensured rights based on disabilities were included in South Africa’s new constitution at the time</string>
    <string name="Q3_A4Beverly">An organization that brought light to issues based on the lack of education about diversity in South Africa\’s schools</string>

    <string name="Q4Beverly">4. Ditsie was the first person, an African lesbian woman to talk, about LGBTQA+ rights at a UN Convention. What specifically did she speak about?</string>
    <string name="Q4_A1Beverly">She spoke about how discrimination based on sexual orientation was a violation of basic human rights and it was necessary to address that before talking about any other concerns of women</string>
    <string name="Q4_A2Beverly">She spoke about the lack of female artists in the music industry</string>
    <string name="Q4_A3Beverly">She spoke about how discrimination based on the ability level was a violation of human rights</string>
    <string name="Q4_A4Beverly">She spoke about how her friends who immigrated to Africa and felt alone</string>

    <string name="Q5Beverly">5. What was Ditsie\’s Film “Simon and I” about?</string>
    <string name="Q5_A1Beverly">Ditsie\’s father Simon, an education activist who passed away due to old age</string>
    <string name="Q5_A2Beverly">Ditsie\’s friend Simon, a disability rights activist who passed away due to their condition</string>
    <string name="Q5_A3Beverly">Ditsie\’s brother Simon, a religious equality activist who passed away due to AIDS</string>
    <string name="Q5_A4Beverly">Ditsie\’s mentor Simon, a gay right’s activist who passed away due to AIDS</string>


    //Malala Yousafzai  Strings

    <string name="MalalaTitle">Malala Yousafzai</string>
    <string name="MalalaBio"> Pronouns: She/Her Gender: Female Age: 23 Activist for Education</string>
    <string name="MalalaInfo1">Malala Yousafzai was born July 12, 1997 in Mingora, Swat valley, Pakistan. She was the daughter of a social activist and an educator. Her father settled and took care of the school she went to, Khushal Girls High School and College. Her father always encouraged her to become educated and follow his path. However, the Swat Valley was invaded in 2007 by the TTP, e Tehrik-e-Taliban Pakistan, who wanted to get rid of any chances for women to play an active role in society and become educated. Yousafzai and her family were forced to flee.
    When she was 11 years old, Yousafzai’s father took her to a press club in Peshawar where she gave her first speech named, “How Dare the Taliban Take Away My Basic Right to Education?”. It became popular all throughout Pakistan and The British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) approached Yousafzai’s father for someone to write blog posts for them about their experience living under TTP rule.  Yousafzai started writing in Urdu, later translated to English, under the name of  Gul Makai. She wrote 35 entires.
    </string>
    <string name="MalalaInfo2">In 2009, Yousafzai  was interviewed for Capital Talk, a Pakistani talk show. Although the TPP was started allowing girls to attend school again, on the condition they wear burkas, violence started again. The New York Times reporter Adam Ellick made a short film with Malala about her school shutting down. Malala became more famous and received Pakistan’s first National Youth Peace Prize. In late 2012, Malala was shot coming home from school by a gunman of the TTP. She survived and her story led to the UN special envoy for global education, Gordon Brown, making a petition to put all children back in school by 2015. This led to the legalization of Pakistan\'s first Right to Education bill. Malala later co-authored the book I Am Malala: The Girl Who Stood Up for Education and Was Shot by the Taliban (2013) with Christina Lamb and became the youngest person to win the Nobel Peace Prize.
    Malala maintained attending school in England and started her own girls school in Lebanon for refugees from the Syrian War using funding from the Malala Fund. In 2020, she finished her Philosophy, Politics and Economics degrees at Oxford. She still continues on her fight for equality and education for everyone today.
    </string>
    <string name="MalalaReferences">https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/malala-yousafzai-graduates-college-8-years-after-taliban-gunned-her-n1231525
        https://www.britannica.com/biography/Malala-Yousafzai</string>

    <string name="Q1Malala">1. What did Yousafzai’s father always encourage her to do?</string>
    <string name="Q1_A1Malala">Follow in his footsteps to become educated and teach</string>
    <string name="Q1_A2Malala">Follow in his footstep to become an artist and spread messages through music</string>
    <string name="Q1_A3Malala">Follow in her friend\’s footsteps to become a doctor</string>
    <string name="Q1_A4Malala">Follow in her uncle\’s footsteps to become an archeologist</string>

    <string name="Q2Malala">2. When she was 11 years old, Yousafzai’s father took her to a press club in Peshawar. She gave a speech that reached the BBC and became very popular throughout the world. What was the name of the speech?</string>
    <string name="Q2_A1Malala">“How Dare the Taliban Take Away My Family?”</string>
    <string name="Q2_A2Malala">“Who am I and why do I do what I do?”</string>
    <string name="Q2_A3Malala">“Who are the Taliban and Why Are They Here?”</string>
    <string name="Q2_A4Malala">“How Dare the Taliban Take Away My Basic Right to Education?”</string>

    <string name="Q3Malala">3. The New York Times reporter Adam Ellick made a short film with Malala about what?</string>
    <string name="Q3_A1Malala">Her family being taken away by the Tehrik-e-Taliban Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Q3_A2Malala">Her public library being shut down by the Tehrik-e-Taliban Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Q3_A3Malala">Her school being shut down by the Tehrik-e-Taliban Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Q3_A4Malala">Her best friends moving to another country</string>

    <string name="Q4Malala">4. What happened in late 2012 when Malala was coming home from school?</string>
    <string name="Q4_A1Malala">She was shot by a gunman from the Tehrik-e-Taliban Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Q4_A2Malala">She befriended a gunman from the Tehrik-e-Taliban Pakistan</string>
    <string name="Q4_A3Malala">She found a dog in the wild to take home</string>
    <string name="Q4_A4Malala">She found money to create her own movie</string>

    <string name="Q5Malala">5. For which of these did Malala use money from the Malala Fund to support?</string>
    <string name="Q5_A1Malala">Her own senior center in New York from veterans from WII</string>
    <string name="Q5_A2Malala">Her own library in Texas for everyone to use</string>
    <string name="Q5_A3Malala">Her own girl\’s school in Lebanon for refugees from the Syrian War </string>
    <string name="Q5_A4Malala">Her own girl\’s school in Pakistan for those who have schools shut down by the Taliban</string>


    //Melanie Campbell Strings

    <string name="MelanieTitle">Melanie Campbell</string>
    <string name="MelanieBio"> Pronouns: She/Her Gender: Female  Anti-Racism and Equal Rights Activist</string>

    <string name="MelanieInfo1">Melanie Campbell was born in Mims, Fla. on the Allantic coast as the youngest of six children. Her parents led the local chapter of the NAACP (National Association for the Advancement of Colored People) organization. They were active in their role and Melanie remembers one night, where was sleeping on the floor, close to her mother and siblings, while her father and a few other men were outside getting ready to defend the town from an attack by the Klu Klux Klan that still existed in the 1950s in Florida.
    Melanie enrolled and graduated from Clark Atlanta University, after she had followed her brothers and sisters, and after graduation she got a job in the corporate world. Despite this, Campbell began missing the activism and the movement and started working for Maynard Jackson, Atlanta’s mayor at the time and a high-profile Black political leader. She ran the mayor\'s office for youth services and hired Stacey Abrams, a student from Spelman College, who asked Jackson about if he really understood the feelings of younger people. Campbell began working hard towards the rise of youth voices.
    </string>

    <string name="MelanieInfo2">Campbell  moved to Washington by 1995 and started working at the National Coalition on Black Civic Participation and in 2000 became the executive director and in 2011 the president and CEO. She spoke about how her life mission was to make sure Black women were not invisible. She was recognized as one of Washington D.C.\'s Top Forty Under Forty Emerging Leaders in 2000. She also convened Black Women’s Roundtable which is a non-partisan organization that is, according to Washington Post, “one of the largest networks of women focused on using civic engagement to improve the lives of Black women, their families and their communities — improving access to health care, ending systemic racism, reforming the criminal justice system, lifting people out of poverty.”
    Campbell’s other accomplishments include convening the Voices of the Electorate National Election Reform Task Force and being a main trainer in 1996 for the West African Women\'s Colloquium in Ghana, West Africa. Currently, she advocates for bringing leadership opportunities for the next generation and bringing equality and fairness, especially for Black girls and women. She has been a features writer at the National Urban League’s State of Black America and has received the “Sustainer of the Flame Freedom Flame Award” by The Bridge Crossing Jubilee.
    </string>

    <string name="MelanieReferences">https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/this-is-how-democracy-crumbles-melanie-campbell-on-the-fight-to-defend-black-votes/2020/11/02/6d2a4884-1d0a-11eb-b532-05c751cd5dc2_story.html
    https://www.ncbcp.org/who/bios/mcampbell/
    https://iop.harvard.edu/fellows/melanie-campbell</string>

    <string name="Q1Melanie">1. When Campbell was growing up in Mims, Florida, her parents led the local chapter of what organization?</string>
    <string name="Q1_A1Melanie">To make sure everyone was well educated about climate change</string>
    <string name="Q1_A2Melanie">To ensure that all people could talk about their favorite subjects in school</string>
    <string name="Q1_A3Melanie">To make sure Black women were not invisible</string>
    <string name="Q1_A4Melanie">To abolish the health care system</string>

    <string name="Q2Melanie">2. What event did Campbell say she remembered where she was sleeping on the floor, close to her brother, sister, and mother while something else was happening?</string>
    <string name="Q2_A1Melanie">Her grandfather going to the grocery store alone because everyone was too tired</string>
    <string name="Q2_A2Melanie">Her father and others ready to defend the town from an attack by the Klu Klux Klan</string>
    <string name="Q2_A3Melanie">Her grandmother was in the hospital after a heart attack</string>
    <string name="Q2_A4Melanie">Her best friend was moving away to another country</string>

    <string name="Q3Melanie">3.  Who did Campbell hire after starting to work for Atlanta\’s Mayor, Maynard Jackson, at the time?</string>
    <string name="Q3_A1Melanie">Joe Jackson because he was a mentor to Campbell and taught her much about politics</string>
    <string name="Q3_A2Melanie">Alexandra Jackson because she was Maynard Jackson\’s daughter</string>
    <string name="Q3_A3Melanie">Michael Jackson because he was famous and well known at the time</string>
    <string name="Q3_A4Melanie">Stacey Abrams because she questioned if Jackson really understood and acknowledged the feelings of younger people</string>

    <string name="Q4Melanie">4. What did Campbell say one of her main life goals was when she became the president and CEO of the National Coalition on Black Civic Participation?</string>
    <string name="Q4_A1Melanie">To make sure everyone was well educated about climate change</string>
    <string name="Q4_A2Melanie">To ensure that all people could talk about their favorite subjects in school</string>
    <string name="Q4_A3Melanie">To make sure Black women were not invisible</string>
    <string name="Q4_A4Melanie">To abolish the health care system</string>

    <string name="Q5Melanie">5. Campbell convened the Black Women’s Roundtable which is a non-partisan organization which is which of the following?</string>
    <string name="Q5_A1Melanie">A network of women to improve the lives of Black women, their families, and communities </string>
    <string name="Q5_A2Melanie">A network of women to spread their favorite books and speak about them</string>
    <string name="Q5_A3Melanie">A weekly meeting in which women discuss career paths and education for seniors</string>
    <string name="Q5_A4Melanie">A weekly meeting in which young Black girls discuss their experiences in life</string>

    //Chad Griffin Strings

    <string name="ChadTitle">Chad Griffin</string>
    <string name="ChadBio"> Pronouns: He/Him Gender: Male  LGTBQ+ Rights Activist</string>

    <string name="ChadInfo1">Chad Griffin was born on July 16, 1973 in Arkansas. He went to school in  Southern Baptist Church and was often bullied and teased for being gay. He was confused about his sexuality by this, admitting to Washington post he did not know he was gay. Growing up, he had a deep passion for international affairs and politics and had one job as a page at the state Capitol.
    He attended Ouachita Baptist University and volunteered for the 1992 presidential campaign of Bill Clinton, dropping out at 19 to become the youngest member of presidential staff. He was at the White House for two years before he started attending Georgetown University\'s School of Foreign Service. Just before he graduated in 1997  he received an offer for a State Department job which he declined when he got an offer from Rob Reiner who was an actor, director, and political activist who he had met in the White House a few years before. He and Reiner established the  I Am Your Child Foundation, a charitable foundation which helped parents and caregivers understand child development better.
    </string>

    <string name="ChadInfo2">Griffin started  his own consulting firm in 1998 and was hired by Reiner to pass Proposition 10 which would put a tax on tobacco products and give the profits to the effects it left on children. He worked on a number of other propositions such as Proposition 71 in 2004 and Proposition 8 in 2008. He was a strong opponent of Propostion 8, which held that only marriage between man and a woman were valid in California, and as an open homosexual, he was deeply upset by the loss. He and Reiner took a different approach the the situation, going to the US Supereme Court and arguing that that marriage is a fundamental right and if same-sex couples were denied it, it would violate the U.S. Constitution\'s guarantee of equal protection. On February 7, 2012, Proposition 8 was ruled unconstitutional.
    Griffin, in 2013, was 16th on Out magazine\'s "Power 50" list of the 50-most powerful LGBT individuals in the United States. Today, Griffin is still a strong activist for LGBTQ+ rights. In 2018, he stepped down as the president of the Human Rights Campaign which he has directed for the past years. He also founded the American Foundation for Equal Rights. Griffin was also a producer for the documentary Outrage which highlighted political figures who had worked against LGBT rights and their allegations and claims against homosexuality.
    </string>

    <string name="ChadReferences">https://peoplepill.com/people/chad-griffin/
    https://apnews.com/article/b872e8f19255470fbb504ef1040df2bf
    https://civilrights.org/2019/04/29/hrcs-chad-griffin-to-receive-chairpersons-award-at-civil-rights-dinner/
    http://www.glbtqarchive.com/ssh/griffin_chad_S.pdf</string>

    <string name="Q1Chad">1. Growing up, Griffin had a deep passion for which subjects?</string>
    <string name="Q1_A1Chad">Math and Science</string>
    <string name="Q1_A2Chad">International affairs and politics</string>
    <string name="Q1_A3Chad">International business and finance</string>
    <string name="Q1_A4Chad">Computer Science and Data Analysis</string>

    <string name="Q2Chad">How many years did Griffin serve in the White House after volunteering in a political campaign at age 19 and under which president?</string>
    <string name="Q2_A1Chad">3 years; Hillary Clinton</string>
    <string name="Q2_A2Chad">2 years; Bill Clinton</string>
    <string name="Q2_A3Chad">5 years; Barack Obama</string>
    <string name="Q2_A4Chad">1 year; Donald Trump</string>

    <string name="Q3Chad">Griffin was a strong opponent of Proposition 8 in 2008 because of his own identity as a gay man. What did Proposition 8 state?</string>
    <string name="Q3_A1Chad">“Eliminates Right of Same-Sex Couples to Marry”</string>
    <string name="Q3_A2Chad">“Eliminates Right of Same-Sex Couples to Appear in Public”</string>
    <string name="Q3_A3Chad">“Right of Same-Sex Couples to Marry”</string>
    <string name="Q3_A4Chad">“Right of Same-Sex Couples to Get Married in a Different Country”</string>

    <string name="Q4Chad">Which campaign did Griffin step down that he had been leading over the past few years?</string>
    <string name="Q4_A1Chad">The National Association for the Advancement of Colored People</string>
    <string name="Q4_A2Chad">Human Rights Campaign</string>
    <string name="Q4_A3Chad">United Nations Free and Equal</string>
    <string name="Q4_A4Chad">Green America</string>

    <string name="Q5Chad">What is the documentary “Outrage”, which Griffin was one of the producers of, about?</string>
    <string name="Q5_A1Chad">Popular authors who wrote about LQBTQ+ during their time</string>
    <string name="Q5_A2Chad">Popular singers who were also part of the LGBTQ+ community and spoke up for their rights</string>
    <string name="Q5_A3Chad">Political figures who had worked against LGBTQ+ rights and their allegations and claims against homosexuality</string>
    <string name="Q5_A4Chad">Political figures who worked for LGBTQ+ rights</string>


    //Jose Antonio Vargas Strings

    <string name="JoseTitle">Jose Antonio Vargas</string>
    <string name="JoseBio"> Pronouns: He/Him Gender: Male Advocating for immigrants and the Latinx community</string>

    <string name="JoseInfo1">Jose Antonio Vargas was born on February 3, 1981 in Antipolo in the Philippines. He was smuggled into the United States at a young age. At the age of 16 when Vargas was going to the DMV to get his license, the clerk informed him it was fake. Vargas went back home and questioned his grandparents who were naturalized American citizens. His grandfather admitted to him that his documents were purchased and fake. From then, Vargas felt like he had to prove his American identity.
    Vargas began watching movies to learn about the culture and aspects of life in America. Hec graduated from Mountain View High School in 2000 and graduated from San Francisco State University in 2004. He was later named Alumnus of the year in 2012. He created multiple works that entail the journey of his life; a New York Times Magazine essay, “My Life as an Undocumented Immigrant”, a Time cover story in 2012, “Not Legal Not Leaving”, and a 2013 film, Documented. Following these works, Vargas wrote a memoir, “Dear America: Notes of an Undocumented Citizen”.
    </string>

    <string name="JoseInfo2">Vargas\’ book follows his journey as a kid who was taken to the US as a 12 year old, his first experiences in America, and his coming out as gay to classmates and grandparents. Vargas often speaks about how as a Filipino, he did not fit in anywhere. When people referred to undocumented immigrants, they usually pointed towards the Latinex community. He noticed irregularities between how people treated illegal immigrants and more.
    In 2015, Vargas\’s documentary, Documented, 2015 NAACP Image Award nomination for Outstanding Documentary. MTV also aired his Emmy Nominated Special, White People, which detailed what it was like to be a young whie child in an America that was changning due to immigration and more. He received the  Freedom to Write Award from PEN Center USA and degrees from Emerson College, Colby College, and the John Jay College of Criminal Justice. He, today, works on an adovisory board for  TheDream.US, which provides scholarships to immigrant students who are undocumented.
    </string>


    <string name="JoseReferences">https://www.theatlantic.com/entertainment/archive/2018/10/dear-america-jose-antonio-vargas-memoir-review/573013/
    https://openborders.info/jose-antonio-vargas-life-story/
    https://joseantoniovargas.com/about/
    </string>

    <string name="Q1Jose">1. What happened to Vargas at a young age?</string>
    <string name="Q1_A1Jose">He had a sister who was taken away because her papers were fake</string>
    <string name="Q1_A2Jose">His parents died in a car crash</string>
    <string name="Q1_A3Jose">He was smuggled into the United States </string>
    <string name="Q1_A4Jose">His grandmother died of cancer</string>

    <string name="Q2Jose">2. How did Vargas begin to learn about American culture after his grandfather admitted to him that his papers were purchased and fake and he felt he needed to fit in?</string>
    <string name="Q2_A1Jose">Watch Hollywood movies</string>
    <string name="Q2_A2Jose">Read all the American literature he could</string>
    <string name="Q2_A3Jose">Thoroughly try to learn every aspect of the English language</string>
    <string name="Q2_A4Jose">Spend time with gangs to learn American slang and culture</string>

    <string name="Q3Jose">3. Which one of these is not a work that Vargas created to show the story of his life?</string>
    <string name="Q3_A1Jose">The New York Times Magazine essay, “My Life as an Undocumented Immigrant”</string>
    <string name="Q3_A2Jose">The essay, “Musings from an Angry Asian American Boy” </string>
    <string name="Q3_A3Jose">A 2021 Time cover story, “Not Legal Not Leaving”</string>
    <string name="Q3_A4Jose">A 2013 film, “Documented”</string>

    <string name="Q4Jose">4. In Vargas/’s memoir, “Dear America: Notes of an Undocumented Citizen”, he talks about what?</string>
    <string name="Q4_A1Jose">His journey of learning how to speak French and the challenges he faced due to his original language</string>
    <string name="Q4_A2Jose">His journey of entering the US as a 12-year-old boy and his experiences of growing up as an undocumented immigrant</string>
    <string name="Q4_A3Jose">His friend/’s journey of growing up as an undocumented citizen and how he helped his friend</string>
    <string name="Q4_A4Jose">The story of his parents/’ journey into Spain as undocumented immigrants and how they overcame their challenges</string>

    <string name="Q5Jose">5. MTV has aired Vargas/’s Emmy Nominated Special, “White People” which is about what?</string>
    <string name="Q5_A1Jose">What it is like to be a young white child in an America that was changing due to immigration policies and other ones as well</string>
    <string name="Q5_A2Jose">What it is like to be a young Latinx child in an America that was changing due to immigration policies and other ones as well</string>
    <string name="Q5_A3Jose">The policies being passed in Congress that discriminated against Black people are their culture</string>
    <string name="Q5_A4Jose">The fight Vargas faced against the government as he advocated for free health rights for all</string>

    //Jamey Jesperson Strings

    <string name="JameyTitle">Jamey Jesperson</string>
    <string name="JameyBio"> Pronouns: He/Him Gender: Male  LGTBQ+ Rights Activist</string>

    <string name="JameyInfo1">Jamey Jesperson was born in California in 1994 to a family of Mormons. Jamey grew up with the idea that they could only be one of two genders, male or female. They were very feminine growing up, playing with toys that people believed only girls played with and hanging out with girls their age. Older men at their church were upset with Jesperson for doing so.
    Jesperson came out as gay in high school and came out as gender non-conforming at the age of 21. They received a lot of gossip as a result of coming out in a large Mormon community but fortunately, at the time, Jesperson was dating someone in a similar situation who helped them. Jesperson\’s parents were supportive of their identity and were always open. Jesperson however got a lot of disgust from the church, with people who started to ignore them and warning their children to stay away from Jesperson.
    </string>

    <string name="JameyInfo2">Jesperson started attending college at The New School in New York City. Jesperson was still following the Mormon faith because from young they had learned that prayer was the only way to deal with emotions such as anger, hate, and loneliness. One day, at church, Jesperson realized they did not want to associate with the church anymore. Many people in Jesperson\’s family were angered by their decision to leave and many of them distanced themself from Jesperson. Despite this, after Jesperson wrote an essay about the Mormon Church\’s anti- LGBTQ+ politics when the Mormon Church separated themselves from Boy Scouts after they started accepting girls, many of their family members supported them.
    Jesperson today is an LGBTQ+ activist who helps make sure that LGBTQ+ youth feel supported and comfortable. They are the Education Associate at GLSEN, which is an organization that works to bring LGBTQ+ students and children with resources they may need and teaches educators how to provide support. Jamey hopes to see youth comfortably identifying outside of the gender binary of male/female or boy/girl. They wish to spread awareness about how society and politics has pushed a rigid gender norm for youth and how it is influencing them.
    </string>

    <string name="JameyReferences">https://www.gaystarnews.com/article/meet-jamey-jesperson-the-nonbinary-activist-who-left-the-mormon-church/
    https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/boy-or-girl-parents-raising-theybies-let-kids-decide-n891836
    https://freedomforallamericans.org/nonbinary-education-activist-we-have-to-embrace-everyones-authenticity/
    </string>

    //Laverne Cox Strings

    <string name="LaverneTitle">Laverne Cox</string>
    <string name="LaverneBio"> Pronouns: She/Her Gender: Female  Trans Representation and Rights Activist</string>

    <string name="LaverneInfo1">Laverne Cox was born on May 29, 1972 in Mobile, Alabama with a twin brother. She was bullied as a child, being called a sissy and the f-word. She did not act the way people assumed a person assigned male at gender would act and many disliked her for it. She was chased after school and beat up. Cox had a suicide attempt at age 11.
    One day, in third grade, Cox\’s teacher told her mother that her son was one day going to be wearing a dress in New Orleans. At the time, Cox did not know the difference between boys and girls, she just assumed she would turn into a girl after puberty. That was the moment she realized she was transgender.
    </string>

    <string name="LaverneInfo2">Cox attended the Alabama School of Fine Arts in Birmingham and studied writing and dance there. She switched to Indiana University Bloomington and then Marymount Manhattan College in New York City when she began to study acting. She is known for her role as Sophia Burset, who is, according to Biography.com, “ an imprisoned trans woman who fights for appropriate hormone treatments and has a highly strained relationship with her son while also receiving love and acceptance from her wife”. In 2008, she was also featured in an episode of Law and Order: SVU and the TV show TRANSform Me (2010).
    Cox was the first trans person to be nominated an Emmy and appear on the cover of Times magazine. As a transgender activst, she has her own panel on the Hufington post and has written an essay on gender identidy and expression named, “Everybody\’s Trans: Gender Oppression Hurts All of Us”. In 2018, Cox became the first transgender woman to appear on the cover of Cosmopoliton, the South Africa edition. She is also the executive producer of Netflix documentary, “Disclosure” which reveals the challenges the trangender community faced over the years, the violence they faced, and movies and other productions that have allowed them to enter the industry.
    </string>

    <string name="LaverneReferences">https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/laverne-cox-details-transphobic-attack-it-s-not-safe-world-n1249334
    https://www.biography.com/actor/laverne-cox
    https://ccrjustice.org/home/blog/2019/08/02/evening-activism-laverne-cox
    https://www.oprahmag.com/entertainment/tv-movies/a28987199/laverne-cox-facts/
    </string>

    <string name="Date">Day</string>
    <string name="ToCalendar">ToCalendar</string>
    <string name="February_8_2021">Meeting at park. Blank meeting at the library</string>
    <string name="February_9_2021">Meeting for the Alemda Country Green Club at 392 Brown Avenue
                                   Plant a tree at the park! Meeting at 9201 Park</string>
    <string name="EventsLabel">Events For the Day</string>
    <string name="DFBtn">DialogFlowButton</string>
    <string name="MainText">Hello! Our AI ChatBot is a chatbot built with DialogFlow using Knowledge Bases. Ask it any questions you have about diversity including questions about race, the LBGTQ+ community, diability rights, education rights, and more. We do not claim the right to any information given by the Chatbot, we have either taken it directly from our sources or paraphrased it. For more information, see a list of our sources on the sources tab in the hamburger.</string>

    //Resources
    <string name="Intro">Resources</string>
    <string name="SuicideCrisis">Suicide And Crisis</string>
    <string name="LYouth">LGBTQ+ Youth</string>
    <string name="DisorderAlliances">Alliances for Disorders</string>
    <string name="call">Call:</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>

    Suicide Crisis
    <string name="ASFP"><a href="https://afsp.org/">The American Foundation for Suicide Prevention</a></string>
    <string name="ASFPd">Provides referrals to support groups and mental health professionals, resources on loss, and suicide prevention information </string>
    <string name="ASFPc">888-333-2377</string>
    <string name="NDVH"><a href="https://www.thehotline.org/">The National Domestic Violence Hotline</a></string>
    <string name="NDVHd">Provides 24/7 crisis intervention, safety planning and information on domestic violence</string>
    <string name="NDVHc">800-799-7233</string>
    <string name="SPL"><a href="https://suicidepreventionlifeline.org/">The Suicide Prevention Lifeline</a></string>
    <string name="SPLd">Connects callers to trained crisis counselors</string>
    <string name="SPLc">800-273-8255</string>

    LGBTQ+
    <string name="TTP"><a href="https://www.thetrevorproject.org/">The Trevor Project</a></string>
    <string name="TTPd">The Trevor Project is the leading national organization providing crisis intervention and suicide prevention services to lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender and questioning (LGBTQ) young people.</string>
    <string name="TTPc">866-488-7386</string>
    <string name="SCO"><a href="https://sco.org/#family-therapy-intervention-pilot-for-lgbtq-youth">SCO Family Therapy Intervention Program</a></string>
    <string name="SCOd">Provides free, short-term family counseling services to support parents and young people in working through challenges that might arise related to coming out.</string>
    <string name="SCOc">516-671-1253</string>
    <string name="TPP"><a href="https://www.mykidisgay.com/">The Parents Project</a></string>
    <string name="TPPd">The Parents Project is a first-of-its-kind digital presence, inclusive of videos, advice, and resources, dedicated exclusively toward helping parents understand their LGBTQ kids.</string>
    <string name="LGBTQmoreinfo"><a href="https://gaycenter.org/resources/#youth">https://gaycenter.org/resources/#youth</a></string>
    <string name="formore">For more information, visit:</string>

    Alliances for Disorders
    <string name="CHADD"><a href="https://chadd.org/">Children and Adults with Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder(CHADD)</a></string>
    <string name="CHADDd">Provides information and referrals on ADHD, including local support groups </string>
    <string name="CHADDc">800-233-4050</string>
    <string name="DBSA"><a href="https://www.dbsalliance.org/">Depression and Bipolar Support Alliance (DBSA)</a></string>
    <string name="DBSAd">Provides information on bipolar disorder and depression, offers in-person and online support groups and forums</string>
    <string name="DBSAc">800-826-3632</string>
    <string name="IOF"><a href="https://iocdf.org/">International OCD Foundation</a></string>
    <string name="IOFd">Provides information on OCD and treatment referrals</string>
    <string name="IOFc">617-973-5801</string>
    <string name="NCEED"><a href="https://www.nceedus.org/">National Center of Excellence for Eating Disorders (NCEED)</a></string>
    <string name="NCEEDd">Provides up-to-date, reliable and evidence-based information about eating disorders</string>
    <string name="NCEEDc">800-931-2237</string>
    <string name="SARDAA"><a href="https://sardaa.org/">Schizophrenia and Related Disorders Alliance of America (SARDAA)</a></string>
    <string name="SARDAAd">Offers Schizophrenia Anonymous self-help groups and toll-free teleconferences</string>
    <string name="SARDAAc">240-423-9432</string>
    <string name="SI"><a href="https://www.sidran.org/">Sidran Institute </a></string>
    <string name="SId">Helps people understand, manage and treat trauma and dissociation; maintains a helpline for information and referrals</string>
    <string name="SIc">410-825-8888</string>
    <string name="TARA"><a href="https://www.tara4bpd.org/">Treatment and Research Advancements for Borderline Personality Disorder</a></string>
    <string name="TARAd">Offers a referral center for information, support, education and treatment options for BPD</string>
    <string name="TARAc">888-482-7227</string>

    RequestForm
    <string name="sendArt">Request For Writing Article</string>
    <string name="req_articleidea">Submit your article topic here</string>
    <string name="req_send">Send</string>
    <string name="req_name">Name</string>
    <string name="req_phone">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="req_address">Address</string>
    <string name="contenthint">I want to submit a piece about ... due to my expriences or research in...</string>

    Calendar Strings
    <string name="Month_1_2021">Zoom meeting for Fremont LGBTQ Alliance club (Link)</string>
    <string name="Month_2_2021">Can Collection at Chase at 29010 Shoresbary Drive</string>
    <string name="Month_3_2021">Clean Lake Elizabeth from 8 to 9 AM
                                Farmer\'s market 9 to 10 AM at 299 Brown Avenue</string>
    <string name="Month_4_2021">No events scheduled for today.</string>
    <string name="Month_5_2021">Marie Ann Fundraiser 5 to 6 PM at Oasis Park</string>
    <string name="Month_6_2021">Drive in Movie: Toy Story 4 to 8 PM at 2910 San Jose Park</string>
    <string name="Month_7_2021">Meditate! by Meditation101 4 to 5 PM (link)</string>
    <string name="Month_8_2021">Meeting at park. Blank meeting at the library</string>
    <string name="Month_9_2021">Meeting for the Alameda Country Green Club at 392 Brown Avenue
                                   Plant a tree at the park! Meeting at 9201 Park</string>
    <string name="Month_10_2021">San Jose Music Collective Club Meeting 8 to 10 AM (Link)</string>
    <string name="Month_11_2021">No events scheduled for today.</string>
    <string name="Month_12_2021">Online Community by YogaGo 3 to 4 PM (Link)
                                 Do you want to be Happy? Webinar by Torry Grey 8 to 10 PM (Link)</string>
    <string name="Month_13_2021">Holiday Inclusion Celebration! by Fremont Events 4 to 5 PM (More information: link.com)</string>
    <string name="Month_14_2021">Community Get-Together by Alameda Country Library (Zoom Link: link)</string>
    <string name="Month_15_2021">Parenting in the New Age Seminar by Mommy and Me 7 to 8 AM (More information: link.com) </string>
    <string name="Month_16_2021">Diversity Inclusion Panel @ UCBerekely 1 to 2 PM (Link)</string>
    <string name="Month_17_2021">Senior Event @ Saratoga Senior Community Center 9 to 10 AM</string>
    <string name="Month_18_2021">Multicultural Cooking Class 3 to 6 PM (Link)</string>
    <string name="Month_19_2021">Diversity Awareness in the Workplace Seminar 2 to 3 PM (Link)</string>
    <string name="Month_20_2021">Black Lives Matter Meeting 6 to 7 PM</string>
    <string name="Month_21_2021">Learning How to be Disability Friendly 5 to 7 PM </string>
    <string name="Month_22_2021">How To Create A Disability Friendly Event Space 2 to 3 PM</string>
    <string name="Month_23_2021">Education Right Around the World Conference 1 to 7 PM</string>
    <string name="Month_24_2021">Religious Rights in the Classroom Discussion 4 to 5 PM</string>
    <string name="Month_25_2021">Famous Advocates Who Fought for Rights! 2 to 5 PM</string>
    <string name="Month_26_2021">Why We Do What We Do by DREDF 10 to 11 AM</string>
    <string name="Month_27_2021">Ways to Combat Your Internal Biases Webinar 8 to 11 AM</string>
    <string name="Month_28_2021">Unpacking White Feminism Lecture by Rachel Cargle</string>
    <string name="Month_29_2021">Forming Alliances in Your Community by Speaker 4 to 8 PM</string>
    <string name="Month_30_2021">Creating a Healthy Environment for LGBTQ+ Students Lecture 6 to 7:30 PM</string>
    <string name="Month_31_2021">Expressing Love For All Club 2 to 3 PM</string>
</resources>
